http://socionicsdating.com/socionicsdating_privacy.shtml

Socionics Dating - Perfect Dating and Matchmaking Service
pay to write my paper
.
iTunes
Privacy Policy for SocionicsDating.com
SocionicsDating.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.SocionicsDating.com.
About SocionicsDating.com and the information we collect
SocionicsDating.com is a web-based introduction service devoted to bringing together people who are perfect for each other. To accomplish this, we must ask for certain personal information. None of the information we gather can be used by the public (visitors, other members, and anyone not employed by SocionicsDating.com or the financial institutions we use to process membership fees) to identify a specific individual.
There are two types of information we collect that users submit: public and private. We define private information to be any information that allows others to contact a user or allows the collection of information about the user other than what is displayed on the site. Public information is personal information that may be displayed on the site, such as gender, age and height, but cannot be linked to a particular user.
Private: This information is gathered from members and users who visit our site. This information includes email addresses.
Public: To accomplish our goal of bringing compatible people together, we must gather personal information such as gender, age, ethnic background, appearance, and more. This information is meant to be seen by members and visitors to the site but cannot be linked by visitors to any private information.
Email Choice/Opt-out
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the email or by logging-in and changing their email options on the Members Page.
How does SocionicsDating.com use your information?
Private: Email addresses submitted by users are used by us when forwarding messages and profiles. Responders' email addresses are not disclosed to the responder. We may use a user's email address to send news regarding our site, but the user may choose not to receive email of this type. Email addresses may also be used in private correspondence with the user for customer service issues. All other private information submitted by the user is confidential. All private information can be updated or deleted by the user at any time by accessing the Manage Your Membership section on the member's page.
Public: Public information supplied by the user is intended to be viewed by visitors to the site. This information is used by visitors for searching and matching purposes. Public information cannot be associated by visitors or other users with any private information.
SocionicsDating.com contains links to other sites.
Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are clicking to another website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.
Sharing the information with third parties
We do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information.
We may disclose Personal Information to other people or agencies in order to
(a) follow the law or comply with legal process served on our affiliates
(b) protect and defend our rights or property or those of our users, and
(c) act as quickly as needed to protect the personal safety of our users or other people.
Using other forms of Information about our users
In addition to the use of Information to operate our site, we may also gather anonymous information, which may be used by us or shared with third parties. This is information which does not personally identify you, but which may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer. (For example, we might use this anonymous information to inform our advertisers how many users visited particular advertisements, and for how long so they can measure whether the advertisement was effective).
Changes in Our Privacy Policy
If our privacy policy changes in a way that will materially affect our users, we will notify them in advance by email.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. This SocionicsDating.com.com database resides behind firewalls in order to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We have taken preventive measures to restrict access to sensitive data, as well as to detect and prohibit certain connections and operations by unauthorized users. While our measures exceed industry standards, no claim is made as to the impenetrability of the system under unusual circumstance or its resilience to future attacks.
We also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
We use different outside credit card processing companies to bill users for goods and services, as well as outside companies to clear and process the credit cards. All of the above mentioned do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Use of Cookies
Despite sensationalized information to the contrary, cookies are not generally a threat to privacy. If we choose to use cookies, we will use them to track items such as unique visitors to a page, or to record which banners have been displayed to a particular user. At times we have paid to advertise on sites other than our own on a click-through basis, and we have used cookies to monitor traffic from those sites on which we advertise. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user!
Delete
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service at the point where their information is collected or
login with your Username and Password on homepage and click button "Delete Your Profile".
Change/Modify
For changing and modifying information previously provided at your Profile you should login with your Username and Password on homepage.
Protect Yourself from Spam
It is a good practice to refrain from disclosing your email address or any other information to other members through our secure message system. Information disclosed may be used by other persons for many purposes, including spamming.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us
if you have any questions.
© 2002-2019 Socionics Dating.com.
All Rights Reserved.
